Kyouma,
I want...
...you to be...
...the messiah.
You want me to be the messiah?
Ridiculous.
I am a mad scientist...
I desire chaos and destruction!
What happened to him?
We will now restart Operation Urd.
Mister Braun's still downstairs, man.
I don't care!
Wait!
I told you.
I'm against this.
Against it?
This morning, you were helping me.
This morning?
Then... I knew it.
Yes.
The experiment took place.
The D-mail has already changed the past.
Seriously?
The world line changed?
Yes, I think so.
Thus, you've lost some
of your memories from before the change.
Is this about that Lotto-6 thing?
That's right.
So why are you the only one who remembers?
Titor told me that I have a power.
To prove it, we need to move world lines again.
A power?
The power to retain memories,
even across world line changes...
The magic eye: Reading Steiner.
Even the number of several billion heartbeats
suujuuoku mo no kodou no kazu sae
anata ni wa matataki teido no saji na toukyuu
is basic research with little glamor for you
kako ni torawarete mirai wo nageku mo
Even locked in the past and lamenting the future
chiri hitotsu gosan wo yurusanu hitsuzen
it's an inevitability that won't forgive miscalculating one speck of dust
mugen ni hirogaru yume mo egaku mirai mo
The dreams that stretch out forever and the future we imagine
bokutachi ni yurusareta kyoei no genri
are a vain theory we allowed
yuugen sore wa futatsu no hari ga shimesu
Finity, that's what the two hands of the clock point out
zankoku na yakujou to sentaku e hacking to the gate
towards a cruel agreement and choice
Hacking to the Gate
zankoku na yakujou to sentaku e hacking to the gate
dakara ima ichibyou goto ni sekaisen wo koete
That's why I want to cross world lines with each passing second
kimi no sono egao mamoritai no sa
and protect your smile
soshite mata kanashimi no nai jikan no loop e to
And once again, into a time loop that contains no sadness
nomikomareteyuku kodoku no kansokusha
A swallowed solitary observer
Chaos Theory
Homeostasis
Daru?
No record in the outbox...
But as for the inbox,
the D-mail arrived five days ago.
It succeeded.
Did the past change?
Why do you remember that?
We sent a D-mail to Daru five days in the past,
telling him the position of the cards,
so he could win the Feyris Cup.
Mayushii?
Question for you... In the Feyris Cup last week...
What? I lost? Immediately?
I see... Thanks. Bye.
Daru's message didn't alter the past.
With the way the game went,
it should have changed.
It wasn't enough to change world lines.
Then we need an easier way to tell
if the past has changed.
I-It still isn't like I agree with
these experiments, okay?
So... What do you think?
About you being the only one to remember?
I told you.
It's the power of the magic eye, Reading Steiner!
In order to see if that's true,
I'll have you send the next D-mail.
I don't want to.
Worried about a time paradox?
It feels unfair to change the past.
I've only lived eighteen years,
but I don't want to change any of them.
They're all part of my life, even the failures.
But you love experiments, right?
I-Is that wrong?
In other words, you'll just sit back and watch,
as others sacrifice themselves.
A true mad scientist.
Enough!
But seriously...
Please
I want to send a D-mail too!
Moeka
But seriously...
If we're going to perfect the D-mail...
Please?
It's okay, right?
Please!
Moeka
...we'll have to continue our experiments...
I'm...
A lab member, too, right?
Moeka
Kiryuu-san?
Enough!
I can't?
She overwhelmed us...
Okay, we're here!
Those crêpes were good...
Yeah.
Hey! You look bored.
I'm waiting for someone.
Hey, don't scare Nae!
I didn't do anything!
Come on, Nae.
Let's leave this loser alone and go inside.
Hi!
Mayuri-oneechan!
I'll give this to you.
Thanks!
Here's one for Okarin, too!
Yo!
Good morning, Suzu-san.
It's the part-timer girl!
Hey... What happened after that?
With what?
The time machine!
Did you ask John Titor?
Yeah, but I don't know if
what he says is accurate...
Which part?
Why are you so interested?
You're a Titor otaku, aren't you?
No.
Kurisu-chan!
Good morning.
More sparks between you two?
What's her problem, anyway?
Fighting makes me sad.
Don't worry! It's okay.
Thank you.
No private messages.
We want something simple, that will make it clear
whether the past's changed.
"I changed my cell phone four days ago,
and I want to tell myself not to do it."
I see.
So if the past changes,
you'll have a different cell phone.
It would be obvious.
Then let us begin the experiment!
Right! Activate the Phone Microwave
(name subject to change)!
It's so round...
What is this?
I used the wrong number for
the Lotto-6 you asked me about.
This is my apology.
I... I see.
Good... Good to hear!
The day nears, when your heart's eye will open.
Yes!
Excuse me, then.
You're leaving?
You seem busy.
Goodbye.
Wear Mayushii's cosplay sometime soon, okay?
I-I'm sorry.
I'm not really into that...
So you won't?
I think you'd look great...
Goodbye.
Bye-bye!
Good kid, huh?
Yeah.
This feeling again.
Which means...
The past changed?
Wh-Where's Shining Finger?
Shi...
Japanese... Do you speak it?
Rukako didn't stop by?
Rukako? Nope.
Then, Moeka... Where's Moeka?
Moeka-san? Who's that?
Kiryuu Moeka!
She wasn't here today?
Well?
Who's that?
Kiryuu Moeka... I've never heard that name.
What?
Another D-mail?
Wh-What do you mean?
The past changed,
and Moeka's very existence disappeared?
Impossible!
Up to July 31st, my inbox still has messages from her.
"Something wrong?"
"Sorry, I'm kind of busy."
"I'll message you later."
In other words,
the past altered in such a way that,
ever since four days ago,
when she received that message,
this Kiryuu... Moeka-san
changed her actions and never came to the lab.
I suppose so.
And this time, only you remember it.
The Reading Steiner, was it?
By the way, just saying that embarrasses me.
I don't think you should call it that.
I'm not interested in your personal opinion.
The power to maintain memories across world lines.
Is it real?
Here I am!
We'll talk tomorrow.
See you tomorrow, Okarin!
I really do have that ability.
I want you to be the messiah.
That means...
I...
I'm amazed they can sleep at the lab...
He said it's 'cause he's a mad scientist.
I know! Let's all sleep over at the lab!
If the guys aren't there.
I know, why not come to my hotel?
Could I?
Of course.
Sure!
Okay, I'll come over soon!
Ruka-kun?
Yeah...
Yeah... What?!
Really?
What?!
You didn't bring the Magic Blade Samidare?
Um...
Don't say that, Okarin!
Today, Ruka-kun is my guest.
He's going to wear my cosplay!
Um... I...
Come on. Let's transform, Ruka-kun. Transform!
Um, I mean, I...
Let's take off your clothes...
No, don't touch me there!
Okay!
I'll put it on myself!
So leave me alone.
You have to know the trick to putting this on.
P-Please... Don't take off my clothes!
This is very yuri.
No. Rukako is a guy.
Which means...
It's even better!
It's Kirari-chan from Rai-Net.
You're as cute as I imagined, Ruka-kun!
This is really embarrassing...
It's okay!
Cute is justice.
I want to get a low-angle shot of this.
What do you think, Okarin?
That's right...
It's me!
I've just been victimized by a
fierce psychological attack!
This is bad!
My soul... My soul is being devoured!
Wh-What's wrong, Kyouma-san?
What's with him?
Kurisu-chan!
Stop staring, pervert assistant.
I'm not staring!
Further win!
What do you think of this cosplay?
Does it look good?
Yes... It's very cute.
C-Cute... Well, I...
Let's try on the others!
Wait!
I came here because I had a request for you.
You didn't come here to wear my cosplay?
I-I said no. But you wouldn't listen to me...
I'm sorry. I was just really happy.
So what did you want to ask?
Actually...
I want you to let me send a message to the past!
I came by...
...to apologize for having missed
the Lotto-6 yesterday. And then...
Another D-mail?
Wh-What do you mean?
The past changed, and Moeka's very existence disappeared?
Impossible!
I'm sorry for listening when I shouldn't have!
I didn't mean to!
Ruka-kun, what kind of message
do you want to send to the past?
Actually, I...
I want to be a girl!
I don't like the way I look.
I think I'd feel better about myself
if I could be a girl...
I've always felt that way.
W-Wait a second...
What is she saying?
Assistant, you appear to have
made a fatal mistake.
Mistake?
Rukako is no girl.
He's a guy.
What kind of joke is that?
You don't believe me...
If you call yourself a scientist,
then see for yourself.
Such a cute girl couldn't be a guy.
Excuse me for a second.
Are you okay?
I'm serious!
I really want to be a girl!
Please!
But I don't know if sending a D-mail
would be enough to change your gender.
I heard of something...
That if you eat lots of meat
when a baby is in your tummy,
you'll have a boy.
With a lot of vegetables, you'll have a girl.
You want us to send a D-mail, telling your mom
to eat lots of vegetables?
Would that be possible?
Very well.
I shall grant your wish.
Thank you!
Good for you, Ruka-kun!
Yes!
Isn't changing someone's gender a bad idea?
Do you think it's possible to affect it,
just by eating vegetables?
That's true.
There's no scientific evidence for it.
He must have really been worried about it
if that makes him feel better.
Rukako, from now on, you're Lab Member 006!
Y-Yes.
Let us begin the experiment...
Wait, you're seventeen this year, right?
Huh? Yes.
In other words, you were born in 1993...
What of it?
When did cell phones become popular in Japan?
It looks like it was around 1996.
And they may only later have
gotten messaging capability.
In other words, when Urushibara-san was born,
there's a good chance his mom
didn't own a cell phone.
Then we can't send the D-mail?
Oh, no.
We could change it, so it sends sinister microwaves.
You have enough sinister microwaves for everyone.
Good... Insult me more.
That's fine...
I see.
I'm terrified by my own talent!
Not this again...
If she doesn't have a cell phone,
send it to her pager!
Pagers...
A system using EM waves to
transmit messages to small receivers.
During the 1990s,
they enjoyed enormous popularity.
The emergence of cellular phones
rendered them obsolete.
Pagers?
I've never seen one!
You're very knowledgeable.
I guess you were a Cel-Pager, not a Cel-7?
It's written right there.
Why not read it yourself?
Lab Member 006, Urushibara Ruka!
It's time for your first mission.
Find out if your mother had a pager.
And get that number!
Y-Yes, sir!
My mom had a pager!
Here's the number.
You did it!
You thought of what to write, right?
Yes!
"Eat vegetables for a healthy child."
I heard you can only send eighteen hiragana...
You can only send numbers to a pager.
Transform these to numbers...
One sec.
You need two digits for voiced consonants.
What?
You can send a total of thirty-six English letters.
That message puts you four characters over.
Then...
Eat veggies for a healthy child.
How about we turn this into numbers?
Okay, starting it up.
All right.
Is this really okay?
Don't worry about it.
My Reading Steiner activated!
Which means...
I see... Some people are like that, huh?
Yes, it's cute!
Ruka-chan, I think you'd look great
in something like this.
Y-You think?
This is...
You pervert!
Where are you staring?
No, I mean...
Wait.
It's difficult to ask if Rukako became a girl.
But...
This failed.
What kind of perverted thing are you imagining?
Jeez, Okarin!
I can't take my eyes off you two perverts for a minute.
I'm not a pervert! I'm a perverted gentlemen!
It doesn't matter... It really doesn't matter!
But...
The world line changed.
Something happened...
But what?
kisei sareta shikai mujihi naru
Our vision, controlled by someone, fills with cruelty
juuni no shihai nogarerarenai
We can't escape the twelve rules
ansoku no asu wo negatta
We wished for a tomorrow full of rest
te no naka no toutoi jishou no chihei he
to be given to the precious event horizon in our hands
toraware shi meiyaku arawareta gishou no rinkaku
In the promise we made in captivity appeared the contours of a lie
seimei no tenchi wa moumoku na jikan wo kizanda
The realm of life recorded a time of blindness
habatake butterfly
Fly, butterfly
kiseki no butterfly
O, miraculous butterfly
anata he sasagu
I will sacrifice to you
namida no butterfly
Butterflies of tears
mabushii butterfly
Dazzling butterflies
subete ga ima kakikaerareru
Everything is being rewritten